back on stage I ain't been on stage in a
while I've been having a rough time I
just going throw it out there had a
rough
2023 so I'm back on stage I'm rough 2023
my unfortunately my brother passed away
in
July yeah then September my wife passed
away so I'm back back on the grind so
y'all bear with me back on that goddamn
she sent the signal down go on get back
on stage do what you do make me goddamn
proud so that's
what back on stage
17 years of beautiful marriage yep we've
been kicking it since '
87 yeah matter of fact when me and my
wife got married I ain't have to get on
one knee and surprise no gay Mar ring I
[\h__\h] just that comfortable we were just
at home looking at TV one day and I just
leaned over I like you know
what we can get mad excited if you want
to I mean if you ain't doing that
she gave me a real cool like back answer
back she was taking the PA of her toes
and didn't even look up she was like all
[Applause]
right I said you know what that's my
[\h__\h] right I [\h__\h] with you [\h__\h] with
you yeah I know she shining down on me
boy this is one time I wish Heaven had
the goddamn FaceTime I need to get I
need to get to her yeah cuz cuz the dude
the dude I took her
from he up
[Applause]
there I don't know if this [\h__\h] was
mapped out or
what she sure left right after that
[Applause]
[\h__\h] oh man I'm telling you like I just
moved to Dallas Texas so I'm just moved
into the house moved into the house I'm
unpacking [\h__\h] I'm keeping great
memories and and then see what [\h__\h] I
want to throw away went through one of
her boxes and found some [\h__\h] yeah I
ain't never seen
before s pay panas I never took
off and I know she used them cuz the tag
off so I'm I got some questions I got
some damn I already told my family when
I Parish put them panties in my sup
jacket so they can go with
me I know she going to try to hug all up
on me like oh [\h__\h] what are
[Applause]
these what are
these cuz that's everybody ultimate goal
when the ending come the end of the day
everybody want to go to heaven everybody
want to go to the upper room go see the
Lord you be hearing folks out there boy
I sure can't wait to go to heaven your
ass can wait you ain't trying to go now
go now I bet you won't go
now you want to see the Lord right now I
bet you won't go now ain't nobody in no
rush to get up there I know one thing
maybe it's the weed I take
in I know one thing they got us going to
church on Sundays reading the Bible
getting on that knee praying Heaven
better be what they say it is it better
be
jumping I better not have not n another
wor when I get up
there I want the same outfit the Lord
wearing whatever thread sheet you got on
I want the same [\h__\h] you stay in the C
the sack put me in
one don't put me don't have me come up
there and talk about you got to start
over now [\h__\h] I was in the full bedroom
here n Don't Put
Me Heaven supposed to be
[Music]
amazing you hear people talking about
boy as soon as I pass I'm going straight
to heaven no you ain't you going to get
your ass in line to get into heaven and
think about it that line long as [\h__\h]
people have been passing away since the
1900s even before they in that line long
than a [\h__\h] to get into heaven
you just feel you better have a fast
pass that ly long as [\h__\h] to get in the
heaven [\h__\h] my Luther King just getting
in
there and he passing
68 we in the Houston still in
line take off on Amigo way back there
[\h__\h] way back that [\h__\h] looking like
this [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] ain't
[Music]
mve they say heaven supposed to be
paradise I feel like we should be able
to leave Heaven on the weekend though I
want to go to H
[Applause]
Friday that's where the hoes
at I guarantee you ain't none of this
going on in
hen ain't none of this [\h__\h] going on in
heaven all right we got 13 more
[\h__\h] coming up tonight man hey
man I'm JJ wion man nothing love all
right y
[Music]